[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He played Dudley Frank in the 2007 movie, Wild Hogs and Tick Tock in the movie Seabiscuit.", "correct_answer": "William H. Macy", "incorrect_answers": ["Strothers Martin", "Tim Allen", "Martin Lawrence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2005 Woody Allen movie about a tennis star discovering the importance of luck over virtue opens with the line, The man who said Id rather be lucky than good saw deeply into life.", "correct_answer": "Match Point", "incorrect_answers": ["Crimes and Misdemeanors", "Vicky Cristina Barcelona", "Scoop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Harvard graduate and Oscar winner for Mister Roberts played the piano, the harmonica and the bass fiddle.", "correct_answer": "Jack Lemmon", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry Fonda", "Oliver Stone", "Billy Wilder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She is a very rude monster.  She sings with her mouth full. What is the name of the human flesh eating plant that sings Feed me Seymour. Feed me all night long.?", "correct_answer": "Audrey II", "incorrect_answers": ["Angel", "Leech Woman", "Christine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When actress Rebecca Schaeffer was murdered by a stalker on July 18, 1989 she had been starring in what TV sitcom?", "correct_answer": "My Sister Sam", "incorrect_answers": ["Murphy Brown", "Major Dad", "My Two Dads"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Matuszak, defensive end for Kansas City Chiefs and Oakland raiders, played a defensive end for the North Dallas team in the movie North Dallas Forty, starring Nick Nolte.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Vitamin E is found in nuts.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actor who played the street performing mime in the movie The Conversation had his own TV show in 1977.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characters in the 2007 film Shrek the Third was voiced by Larry King?", "correct_answer": "Doris the ex/evil stepsister", "incorrect_answers": ["Cyclops", "King Harold", "The Ship Captain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country has Bratislava as its capital city, and the koruna as its unit of currency?", "correct_answer": "Slovakia", "incorrect_answers": ["Slovenia", "Macedonia", "Latvia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the reproduction of the Aye-aye?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The baby stays with its mother for a year.", "Pregnancy lasts about 4 months.", "It reaches reproductive age at 3 - 3.5 years."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the movie The Pursuit of Happyness set?", "correct_answer": "in the San Francisco area", "incorrect_answers": ["in the Seattle  area", "in the Denver area", "in the Los Angeles area"]}]